<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WildwoodMo.com - A Wildwood Missouri Community Site.</title>
    <description>An unofficial website dedicated to information about the City of Wildwood Missouri.
</description>
    <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.wildwoodmo.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:35:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Voting information for Wildwood, Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This page has a collection of voting information for Wildwood, Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;election-day-date&quot;&gt;Election Day Date&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Election Day is Tuesday, November 8, 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;election-day-time&quot;&gt;Election Day Time&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When can you vote in St. Louis County? 6:00 AM to 7:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;voting-locations&quot;&gt;Voting Locations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In St. Louis County you can vote at any voting location, you no longer need to go to a specific location based on where you live. So feel free to try multiple locations if the first location you go to is too busy. You can also vote at locations near your office if you are out and about (assuming those locations are in St. Louis County and you’re a county resident).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find your closest voting location here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://stlouiscovotes.maps.arcgis.com/apps/instant/nearby/index.html?appid=d8d8ebf24d3b4c8cadabf126b72061fb&quot;&gt;St. Louis County Election Board&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;absentee-voting&quot;&gt;Absentee Voting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No excuses in-person absentee voting began on October 25th, 2022. You can vote absentee in person at the Board Of Elections. &lt;a href=&quot;https://stlouiscountymo.gov/st-louis-county-government/board-of-elections/elections/absentee-voting/&quot;&gt;More information on Absentee voting can be found here&lt;/a&gt;.
The last day to vote absentee is 11/7/2022 at 5pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;board-of-elections-website&quot;&gt;Board of Elections Website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Board Of Elections website can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;https://stlouiscountymo.gov/st-louis-county-government/board-of-elections/&quot;&gt;https://stlouiscountymo.gov/st-louis-county-government/board-of-elections/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;testing-of-tabulation-equipment&quot;&gt;Testing of Tabulation Equipment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stlouiscountymo.gov/st-louis-county-government/board-of-elections/temporary/faqs/&quot;&gt;From the St. Louis County FAQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In preparation for the November 8, 2022 General Election, the St. Louis County Board of Elections will conduct a test of the Verity tabulating equipment beginning at 9:00 am on Wednesday, November 2, 2022 at 725 Northwest Plaza Dr., St. Ann, MO. The test will be open to representatives of the political parties, candidates, the news media, and the public. The test will be conducted by processing a pre-audited group of test votes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/10/26/voting-in-wildwood-missouri.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/10/26/voting-in-wildwood-missouri.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wildlife in Wildwood Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What kind of wildlife can you find in Wildwood Missouri?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a list:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rabbits (bunnies)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Raccoons&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Possum&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Squirrels&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cats&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coyotes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bobcats (maybe?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What else have you found in Wildwood?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/07/26/wildlife-in-wildwood.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/07/26/wildlife-in-wildwood.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Murder at Larry's Tavern</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;News on the morning of April 20th is saying that there was a shooting at Larry’s Tavern in Wildwood late on 4/19/2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Details are sparse, but it apparently was outside, with two dead. Possibly a 51 year old male, killed a 40 year old male, then turn the gun on himself.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/04/20/murder-at-larrys-tavern.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/04/20/murder-at-larrys-tavern.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rockwood Board Of Education Election April 5th, 2022</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for information on the candidates for Rockwood School District in Missouri’s election to the board of education on April 5th, 2022, look no further!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything you need to know is in this graphic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/article_images/rsdmocandidates.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;April 5th Candidates&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be sure to &lt;a href=&quot;https://tinyurl.com/2p8wdec4&quot;&gt;Watch the League Of Women Voters Candidate Forum&lt;/a&gt; an informative session of 4 of the 5 candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rnea.org/&quot;&gt;More info about the Rockwood NEA - Rockwood National Education Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research the candidates. Make the right decision for Rockwood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vote for Stine and Ryan!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- If you think CRT is in our schools, and is the biggest threat to our schools, you're paranoid and need to actually do some research to understand that Rockwood doesn't use, or plan to use, CRT. 

CRT is a right wing scare tactic that people who like to ban books use to get you worked up over issues that don't exist. --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/03/15/rockwood-board-of-education-april-5-2022.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/03/15/rockwood-board-of-education-april-5-2022.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Movie Theater in Wildwood, Missouri</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/01/13/wildwood-missouri-movie-theater.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2022/01/13/wildwood-missouri-movie-theater.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bicycling in Wildwood Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for places to ride your bike near St. Louis, you will be hard pressed to find a better area for all types of riding than Wildwood, Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;mountain-biking&quot;&gt;Mountain Biking&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the best mountain biking in the St. Louis area can be found right here in Wildwood. Be sure to visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://gorctrails.com/trails/bluff-view&quot;&gt;Bluff View, Zombie, Rock Hollow&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://gorctrails.com/trails/greensfelder&quot;&gt;Greensfelder&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GORC (Gateway Off-road Cyclists) has really put in a lot of effort into the park at Bluff View and is currently building out new trails and kids trails there as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;road-cycling&quot;&gt;Road Cycling&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for beautiful roads to ride your road or tri bike on, Wildwood is the place for you! We’ve got plenty of hills with climbs to earn your descents. You can easily get one thousand feed of climbing in with a 10 mile route or even more climbing for longer routes as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the safest places to ride your road bike include Centaur Road, often used for time trials, or around Babler State Park which has some of the infamous Babler Beast climb with two different loop options to get you around the park with a bit of variety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wildhorse Creek road is a popular cycling route, connecting over to Ossenfort for a climb up towards Highway T and ultimately connecting over to Melrose. From Melrose you can easily get to Greensfelder park, or take another climb up through Rockwood Reservation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to beautiful roads Wildwood has miles and miles of paved multi-use trails that get you around the city safely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;gravel-grinding&quot;&gt;Gravel Grinding&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Wildwood has grown up, more and more pavement has replaced gravel around the city, but there are still a number of options if you’re looking to scratch your gravel itch. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://gorctrails.com/trails/al-foster-trail&quot;&gt;Al Foster&lt;/a&gt; is a great local trail, but if you really want to ride gravel your best bet is to park at the LeCave trailhead down on Centaur Road and ride ~4 miles over to the Katy Trail in St. Charles County. From LeCave you can ride about 9 miles (west on the Katy) to the Hamburg trail and get a nice gravel climb up into Busch Wildlife where you can find miles and miles of gravel roads and loops to ride around on.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2021/09/28/Bicycling-in-Wildwood-Missouri.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2021/09/28/Bicycling-in-Wildwood-Missouri.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fireworks in Wildwood, Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for Fireworks in Wildwood, Missouri for July 4th, 2021 you’ll need to look a little further east, or head to the north.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The closest shows you will find for the Fourth of July will be at Blue Bird Park in Ellisville, Missouri, or up in Chesterfield, Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ellisville.mo.us/247/Independence-Day-Festivities&quot;&gt;Blue Bird Park Fireworks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chesterfield.mo.us/4th-of-july-fireworks-celebration-2021.html&quot;&gt;Chesterfield Athletic Complex Fireworks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2021/07/04/fireworks-in-wildwood-missouri.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2021/07/04/fireworks-in-wildwood-missouri.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trash Service from the Snow Storm February 2021</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With all the weather we’ve received over the past couple of weeks, Waste Connections has definitely struggled to keep up. Trash Service should be back to normal as of 2/22/2021, though they will be picking up extra amounts of trash as many customers didn’t get serviced last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you continue to have problems with getting your trash picked up, please be sure to reach out to Waste Connections via the link at the bottom of this post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of tips, make sure you are signed up for their website and phone notifications. For the most part they provided great communication around service in the past week via phone calls, though sometimes those calls came in at very late hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wasteconnectionsmo.com/&quot;&gt;Waste Connections of Missouri Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2021/02/22/trash-service-in-wildwood-missouri-february-2021-snow.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2021/02/22/trash-service-in-wildwood-missouri-february-2021-snow.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trash Service in Wildwood, Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Since the summer of 2019, trash service in Wildwood Missouri has been provided by Waste Connections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both trash and recycling services are provided by Waste Connections, your pickup days will vary based on your location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for large item pickup, for a couch, or other things, be sure to check with Waste Connections to get that scheduled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wasteconnectionsmo.com/&quot;&gt;Waste Connections of Missouri Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2020/12/06/trash-service-in-wildwood-missouri.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2020/12/06/trash-service-in-wildwood-missouri.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to WildwoodMo.com!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a website about the City of Wildwood, Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 18:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2020/11/16/welcome-to-wildwoodmo.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wildwoodmo.com/2020/11/16/welcome-to-wildwoodmo.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
